

NNAMDI OKPALA

Contact

 $\frac{\text{okpalan@protonmail.com}}{+4407488229054}$

Education

2 Diploma IT User Skills

South Essex College of further and Higher Education

South Essex College Level 2 IT User Skills

EDX-Microsoft cooperation -Verified certificate on Designing a technical solution Remote

EDX-Microsoft cooperation-Building interactive prototypes using Java script

Remote

New Skills Academy, CSS Certificate, HTML, Java Certificate, Programming Certificate, Python Certificate MC,C++, jQuery Certificate, Level 2 HTML5 AND CSS 2.

Remote

Socials:

https://www.github.com/okpalan nhttps://www.youtube.com/okpalan anx.com/okpalanx instagram.com/okpalanx https://okpalanx.blogspot.com/

Professional summary

Firstly, I am a full stack software engineer knowledge on the implementation of Data Structure and Algorithms. After the purchase of a family Nintendo, which drove my curiousity. I have honed my problem solving, and programming skills on a various of devices. This includes a Raspberry PI (Model B), Laptops, Smart Mobile and Desktop.

Secondly, I have obtained verified certificates of achievements with Microsoft in building interactive prototypes using JavaScript, and in designing a technical solution. I am making the most of my opportunities to become a software engineer and teaching others how to computer program.

I attended the oxford university at the young age of 14 which I completed a unit-based courses given by the university as assessment to progress in as part of a group called the Gifted and Talented (GNT).

Thirdly, I am experienced in the MEVN (MongoDB, Express, Vue and NodeJS). In my leisure, I have made some YouTube Videos which shows some of my knowledge and skills which can be located at youtube.com/@okpalan. I leverage social media to tell my story.

With my Autism, ADHD, I look for both unconventional, and conventional solution to problems. In addition, I can design logos, create beautiful **digital**, and **traditional** painting. In my spare, I create artwork using systematic, and methodological approach which I can refine to gain insight through survey, polls, and questionnaires. I bring my work to life through animations using both opensource and proprietary software (Clip Studio Paint, Moho,etc).

Work history

New Skills Academy 12/2018 - 05/2019

- Coding and studying online
- Analyzed data and information to identify issues and create tailored solutions.

05/2019 - Completed

- Motivated Learning and Making You Tube Coding Training Videos online on
- · Object oriented programming,
- Interphases and constructor in JavaScript,
- OOP Concepts, polymorphism and more and Classes and Name Spaces https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCfR4UKfueYq6M0jnqjFjWog
- @softdeck4451
- Using Gitlab and GitHub to commit to a font end application written in node.js
- I acquired these skills reading online documentation, and taking online courses
- I also acquired some of these skills when at work experience building Northgate User Page
- I can now use git service to commit code onto a certain branch.

10/2018 - 01/2019

- Future coders work experience Programmer Participation
- App development for clients
- Planning and problem solving.
- Certificate of Completion

Thurrock Council 06/2016 - 06/2016

• Experience, meeting coordinator, Booking Meetings, Allocating meeting rooms

Skills

- Microsoft Office Suite, Excel, Word, Outlook.
- JavaScript, C, Python.
- HTML5, CSS, Node, XML, PHP, AJAX.
 Python Programming, Lua Scripting.
 Type Script Programming, Basic Linux
 Scripting Knowledge, C
- KEY Skills/ Achievements TECHNICAL Skills
- Excellent communication
- Team working
- Problem-Solving

- Training and Development
- Critical Thinking
- Self-Motivated
- Written Communication
- Decision-Making
- Communication skills
- Time management
- Digital Art
- Traditional Art
- Theory

Languages

English

Expert (Non-Native)